Steve McQueen going down his own road, tougher than ever, as "Junior Bonner"
Junior Bonner is a western, drama film directed by Sam Peckinpah.
With his bronco-busting career on its last legs, Junior Bonner heads
to his hometown to try his luck in the annual rodeo.
But his fond childhood memories are shattered when he finds his family
torn apart by his greedy brother and hard-drinking father.
Junior Bonner, played by Steve McQueen.
Ace Bonner, played by Robert Preston.
Elvira Bonner, played by Ida Lupino.
Buck Roan, played by Ben Johnson.
Curly Bonner, played by Joe Don Baker.
Charmagne, played by Barbara Leigh.
Junior Bonner is a 1972 American contemporary Western film directed by Sam Peckinpah and
starring Steve McQueen, Robert Preston, Joe Don Baker, and Ida Lupino.
The film focuses on a veteran rodeo rider as he returns to his hometown of Prescott, Arizona, to
participate in an annual rodeo competition and reunite with his brother and estranged parents.
Many critics consider it to be the warmest and most gentle of Peckinpah's films.
The film explores themes of rodeo, arizona, jeep, womanizer, truck.
The tone is emotional.